Finding Aid for Angela Morgan Papers 1861-1957
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Artifacts
  - Angela Morgan's lock of hair (Box 61)
December 5, 1910, January 3, 1911, January 18, 1911, January 31, 1911, February 3, 1911, February 18, 1911, March 23, 1911, March 26, 1911, March 29, 1911, April 5, 1911, April 18, 1911, April 19, 1911, April 28, 1911, May 6, 1911, June 19, 1911, June 20, 1911, September 5, 1911, November 18, 1911, January 18, 1912, January 26, 1912, February 2, 1912, August 9, 1912, September 3, 1912, November 2, 1912, April 1, 1913, April 4, 1913, April 16, 1913, May 15, 1913, June 11, 1913, June 14, 1913, June 17, 1913, June 18, 1913, June 19, 1913, June 24, 1913, June 30, 1913, June 23, 1913, July 1, 1913, July 8, 1913, July 26, 1913, April 22, 1913, August 7, 1913, September 3, 1913, September 12, 1913, October 3, 1913, November 12, 1913, December 31, 1913, December 13, 1913, 1914 1918, undated, January 12, 1914, January 16, 1914, January 19, 1914, January 23, 1914, February 9, 1914, February 24, 1914, March 12, 1914, April 6, 1914, August 25, 1914, September 13, 1914, July 26, 1915, November 16, 1915, February 29, 1916, October 7, 1916, October 18, 1916, December 22, 1916, June 7, 1917, June 14, 1917, January 22, 1918, December 31, 1918, October 1, 1919, October 6, 1919, October 15, 1919, October 29, 1919, November 25, 1919, March 19, 1920, April 12, 1920, January 3, 1921, January 10, 1921, January 12, 1921, January 20, 1921, April 26, 1921, May 1, 1921, February 5, 1924, March 22, 1924, May 3, 1924, May 27, 1924, September 24, 1924, October 30, 1924, December 5, 1924, December 8, 1924, October 3, 1925, February 11, 1926, February 23, 1926, April 2, 1926, April 7, 1926, May 3, 1926, May 7, 1926, October 26, 1926, February 20, 1929, December 18, 1929
Wilson, Woodrow, [subject] 1856-1924
September 10, 1916 from Rebecca Shelly
Women's International League for Peace and Freedom
March 14, 1923, January 20, 1930, June 3, 1930, November 10, 1930, March 29, 1935, April 8, 1935, April 22, 1935, December 7, 1938, August 29, 1939
Woman's Peace Party
April 8, 1915, December 21, 1916, January 8, 1917, February 9, 1917, March 3, 1917, April 10, 1917, September 24, 1917, September 28, 1917, October 22, 1917, November 28, 1917, December 14, 1917, January 23, 1918, April 29, 1918, June 8, 1918, June 12, 1918, August 15, 1918, September 25, 1918, September 28, 1918, October 17, 1918
The Woman's Pro-League Council
December 18, 1921
Women's National Committee for Hands off the Supreme Court
November 18, 1937, November 30, 1937, December 10, 1937
Women's Peace Society
July 11, 1922
Wood, L Hollingsworth
December 16, 1931
The World's Court League, Inc.
May 7, 1918
Young, William Wesley, 1868-
November 27, 1911, December 29, 1911, September 16, 1913, December 22, 1917, January 17, 1918, February 24, 1918, April 13, 1918